Stephen J. Gould papers M1437
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Manuscripts
  - Books
    - Wonderful Life: The Burgess Shale and the Nature of History
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 2 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 3 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapters 1 and 2 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Preface and Acknowledgments (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 3, Acts 4 and 5 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 3, Act 5 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 3, Summary Statement on the Bestiary... (2 folders) (Box-folder 168-10, Box-folder 168-11)
      - Wonderful Life, tape corrected typescript, Chapter 3 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 4 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 4 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, Chapter 5 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Wonderful Life, typescript, annotated (4 folders) (Box-folder 169-3, Box-folder 169-6)
      - Wonderful Life, galley proofs, miscellaneous (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Wonderful Life, galley proofs, typescript, Index (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Wonderful Life, master galley proof set (second pass) (4 folders) (Box-folder 170-1, Box-folder 170-4)
      - Wonderful Life, master galley proof set (confirmation) (4 folders) (Box-folder 170-5, Box-folder 170-8)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (2 folders) (Box-folder 170-9, Box-folder 170-10)
      - Wonderful Life, figure list (Box 170, Folder 11)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (Half-box 171, Folder 1)
      - Wonderful Life, figures, artwork (Half-box 171, Folder 2)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Wonderful Life, figures, Walcott's Diary (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (2 folders) (Box-folder 172-3, Box-folder 172-4)
      - Wonderful Life, proof (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (2 folders) (Box-folder 172-6, Box-folder 172-7)
      - Wonderful Life, research and notes (5 folders) (Box-folder 173-1, Box-folder 173-5)
      - Wonderful Life, research and notes (6 folders) (Box-folder 174-1, Box-folder 174-6)
      - Wonderful Life, correspondence (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Wonderful Life, review by Simon Conway Morris and rebuttal by Gould (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (3 folders) (Box-folder 175-1, Box-folder 175-3)
      - Wonderful Life, design proofs, figures and correspondence (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Wonderful Life, research and notes, Walcott (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Wonderful Life, Canadian research trip materials (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Wonderful Life, master galley proof set (first pass) (3 folders) (Box-folder 175-7, Box-folder 175-9)
      - Wonderful Life, dust jackets (Box 175, Folder 10)
      - Wonderful Life, dummy proof/pasteup (Flat-box 216)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Odontogriphus (Half-box 237, Folder 1)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Ayesheaia (Half-box 237, Folder 2)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Canadia (Half-box 237, Folder 3)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Amiskwia (Half-box 237, Folder 4)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Ottoia (Half-box 237, Folder 5)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Sarotrocercus (Half-box 237, Folder 6)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Yohoia (Half-box 237, Folder 7)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Pikaia (Half-box 237, Folder 8)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Odaraia (Half-box 237, Folder 9)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Canadaspis (Half-box 237, Folder 10)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Nectocaris (Half-box 237, Folder 11)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Dinomischus (Half-box 237, Folder 12)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Opabinia (Half-box 237, Folder 13)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Leanchoilia (Half-box 237, Folder 14)
      - Wonderful Life, figures - Wixwaxi (Half-box 237, Folder 15)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (Half-box 237, Folder 16)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (3 folders) (Box-folder 267-6, Box-folder 267-8)
      - Wonderful Life, publicity (Box 267, Folder 9)
      - Wonderful Life, cover design (Box 363, Folder 8)
      - Wonderful Life, clippings (3 folders) (Box-folder 363-9, Box-folder 363-11)
      - Wonderful Life, figure proofs (Box 363, Folder 12)
      - Wonderful Life, figures (assorted) (Box 363, Folder 13)
      - Wonderful Life, publicity (Box 363, Folder 14)
      - Wonderful Life, dust jacket (Box 459, Folder 12)
      - Wonderful Life, international reviews (Box-folder 459-13, Box-folder 459-14)
      - Wonderful Life, reviews/clippings (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - Bully for Brontosaurus
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, draft (6 folders) (Box-folder 176-1, Box-folder 176-6)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, draft (6 folders) (Box-folder 176-7, Box-folder 176-9, Box-folder 177-1, Box-folder 177-3)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, typescript/manuscript, Prologue (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, typescripts, Epilogue (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, typescript, Bibliography (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, typescript, Index (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, typescript, Bibliography (Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, galley proof (6 folders) (Box-folder 177-9, Box-folder 177-13)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, dust jacket (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, dust jacket (Box 260, Folder 11)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, clippings (Box 360, Folder 5)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, non-querty keyboard photographs (Box 360, Folder 6)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, clippings (Box-folder 360-7, Box-folder 360-8 (2 folders))
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, dust jacket (Box 360, Folder 9)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, publicity (Box 360, Folder 10)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, reviews and clippings (Box 457, Folder 5)
      - Bully for Brontosaurus, publicity posters (Flat-box 515, Folder 17)
    - Full House: The Spread of Excellence From Plato to Darwin
      - Full House, typescript, Chapter 1 (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Full House, partial typescripts, Chapter 1 (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Full House, typescript, Chapter 2 (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Full House, partial typescripts, Chapter 4 (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Full House, typescript (3 folders) (Box-folder 184-5, Box-folder 184-7)
      - Full House, tables (Box 184, Folder 8)
      - Full House, typescript, Bibliography (Box 184, Folder 9)
      - Full House, typescript, Why the Death of 0.400 Hitting Records Improvement of Play (Box 184, Folder 10)
      - Full House, typescript (Box 301, Folder 1)
      - Full House, first pass galley proofs (1 of 2) (Box 301, Folder 2)
      - Full House, first pass galley proofs (2 of 2) (Box 301, Folder 3)
      - Full House, publicity (Box 301, Folder 4)
      - Full House, partial typescript (Life’s Grandeur) (Box 301, Folder 5)
      - Full House, research and notes – sports (Box 301, Folder 6)
      - Full House, research and notes (Box 301, Folder 7)
      - Full House, research and notes (Box 301, Folder 8)
      - Full House, typescript (Box 301, Folder 9)
      - Full House, partial annotated author’s first pass galley proofs (Box 301, Folder 10)
      - Full House, partial annotated typescript and notes (Box 302, Folder 1)
      - Full House, annotated typescripts (Box 302, Folder 2)
      - Full House, drafts and notes (Box 302, Folder 3)
      - Full House, drafts and notes (Box 302, Folder 4)
      - Full House, annotated galley proof (1 of 2) (Box 302, Folder 5)
      - Full House, annotated galley proof (2 of 2) (Box 302, Folder 6)
      - Full House, author’s second pass galley proof - figures (Box 302, Folder 7)
      - Full House, jacket design (Box 361, Folder 3)
      - Full House, draft of flap copy (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - Full House, introduction and illustrations, second pass, annotated (Box 361, Folder 5)
      - Full House, cover proof (Box 361, Folder 6)
      - Full House, figures (Flat-box 434, Folder 2)
      - Full House, correspondence (Box 457, Folder 19)
      - Full House, reviews (clippings) (Box 458, Folder 1)
      - Full House (including Life's Grandeur), reviews (Box 458, Folder 2)
      - Full House, typescript, The Spread of Excellence (Box-folder 458-3, Box-folder 458-4)
    - Dinosaur in a Haystack: Reflections in Natural History
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, notes and outline (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Late Birth of a Flat Earth (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Monster's Human Nature (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Sweetness and Light (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, In the Mind of the Beholder (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Cordelia's Dilemma (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Lucy on the Earth in Stasis (Box 183, Folder 7)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Dinosaur in the Haystack (Box 183, Folder 8)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Jove's Thunderbolts (Box 183, Folder 9)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Poe's Greatest Hit (Box 183, Folder 10)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Invisible Woman (Box 183, Folder 11)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Left Snails and Right Minds (Box 183, Folder 12)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Dinomania (Box 183, Folder 13)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Cabinets Museums (Box 183, Folder 14)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Razumousky Duet (Box 183, Folder 15)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Four Antelopes of the Apocalypse (Box 183, Folder 16)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Smoking Gun of Eugenics (Box 183, Folder 17)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Most Unkindest Cut of All (Box 183, Folder 18)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Can We Complete Darwin's Revolution? (Box 183, Folder 19)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, A Humongous Fungus Among Us (Box 183, Folder 20)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Hooking Leviathan by Its Past (Box 183, Folder 21)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, A Special Fondness for Beetles (Box 183, Folder 22)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Magnolias from Moscow (Box 183, Folder 23)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Ordering Nature by Budding... (Box 183, Folder 24)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, notes (Box 260, Folder 12)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Dousing Diminutive Dennis's Debate (or DDDD = 2000) (Box 260, Folder 13)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Can We Complete Darwin's Revolution? (Box 260, Folder 14)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Lucy on the Earth in Stasis (Box 260, Folder 15)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, The Invisible Woman (Box 260, Folder 16)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, photos (Box 360, Folder 11)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, publicity (Box 360, Folder 12)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Can We Complete Darwin's Revolution (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Celestial Mechanic and the Earthly Naturalist (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Come Seven (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Cordelia's Dilemma (Box 417, Folder 4)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, correspondence (Box 417, Folder 5)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Dinomania (Box 417, Folder 6)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, A Dinosaur in the Haystack (Box 417, Folder 7)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Does the Stoneless Plum Instruct the Thinking Reed (Box 417, Folder 8)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Dousing Diminutive Dennis's Debate (Box 417, Folder 9)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Epilog to Essay 16 (Box 417, Folder 10)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Epilog to Essay 24 (Box 417, Folder 11)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Epilog to Essay 28 (Box 417, Folder 12)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Evolution by Walking (Box 417, Folder 13)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The First Unmasking of Nature (Box 417, Folder 14)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Four Antelopes of the Apocalypse (Box 417, Folder 15)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Four Metaphors in Three Generations (Box 417, Folder 16)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Happy Thoughts on a Sunny Day in New York City (Box 417, Folder 17)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Hooking Leviathan By Its Past (Box 417, Folder 18)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, A Humongous Fungus Among Us (Box 417, Folder 19)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated transcript, If Kings Can Be Hermits, Then We Are All Monkeys' Uncles (Box 417, Folder 20)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, In the Mind of the Beholder (Box 417, Folder 21)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Invisible Woman (Box 417, Folder 22)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Jove's Thunderbolts (Box 417, Folder 23)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Late Birth of a Flat Earth (Box 417, Folder 24)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Left Snails and Right Minds (Box 417, Folder 25)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Lucy on the Earth in Stasis (Box 417, Folder 26)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Magnolias From Moscow (Box 417, Folder 27)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Monster's Human Nature (Box 417, Folder 28)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Most Unkindest Cut of All (Box 417, Folder 29)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Of Tongue Worms, Velvet Worms, and Water Bears (Box 417, Folder 30)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Ordering Nature by Budding and Full-Breasted Sexuality (Box 417, Folder 31)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Poe's Greatest Hit (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, typescript, Preface (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, proofs and correspondence (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Razumovsky Duet (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, review/response by Gould (Box 418, Folder 5)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, reviews/clippings (Box 418, Folder 6)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Speaking of Snails and Scales (Box 418, Folder 7)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, A Special Fondess for Beetles (Box 418, Folder 8)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Sweetness and Light (Box 418, Folder 9)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, Table of Contents (Box 418, Folder 10)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, The Tooth and the Claw Centennial (Box 418, Folder 11)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Cabinet Museums: Alive, Alive, O! (Box 457, Folder 7)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Come Seven (Box 457, Folder 8)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, A Dinosaur in a Haystack (Box 457, Folder 9)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Hooking Leviathan By Its Past (Box 457, Folder 10)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Jove's Thunderbolts (Box 457, Folder 11)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Lucy on the Earth in Stasis (Box 457, Folder 12)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Sweetness and Light (Box 457, Folder 13)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript, Table of Contents (Box 457, Folder 14)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, various annotated typescripts (Box 457, Folder 15)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, copyedited/first pass proof and correspondence (2 folders) (Box-folder 490-1, Box-folder 490-2)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, annotated typescript (3 folders) (Box-folder 490-3, Box-folder 490-5)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, galley proof (Box 490, Folder 6)
      - Dinosaur in a Haystack, galley proof (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - Eight Little Piggies: Reflections in Natural History
      - Eight Little Piggies, informal proposal (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Eight Little Piggies, outline and published Natural History Magazine articles (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Eight Little Piggies, Table of Contents (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Eight Little Piggies, Prologue (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Unenchanted Evening (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Golden Rule (Box 178, Folder 6)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Losing a Limpet (Box 178, Folder 7)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Eight Little Piggies (Box 178, Folder 8)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Bent Out of Shape (Box 178, Folder 9)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, An Earful of Jaw (Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Full of Hot Air (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Men of the Thirty-Third Division (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Darwin and Paley Meet... (Box 178, Folder 13)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, More Light on Leaves (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, On Reading Edmund Halley (Box 178, Folder 15)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Fall in the House of Ussher (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Muller Bros. Moving & Storage (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Shoemaker and Morning Star (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, In Touch with Walcott (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Counters and Cable Cars (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Mozart and Modularity (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Moral State of Tahiti--and of Darwin (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Ten Thousand Acts of Kindness (Box 179, Folder 8)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Declining Empire of Apes (Box 179, Folder 9)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Wheel of Fortune and the Wedge of Progress (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Tires to Sandals (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Defending the Heretical and the Superfluous (Box 179, Folder 12)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Reversal of Hallugencia (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, What the Immaculate Pigeon Teaches (Box 179, Folder 14)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, The Great Seal Principle (Box 179, Folder 15)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, A Dog's Life in Galton's Polyhedron (Box 179, Folder 16)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Betting on Chance - And No Fair Peeking (Box 179, Folder 17)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, Shields of Expectation - And Actuality (Box 179, Folder 18)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, A Tale of Three Pictures (Box 179, Folder 19)
      - Eight Little Piggies, annotated article, A Foot Soldier for Evolution (Box 179, Folder 20)
      - Eight Little Piggies, Bibliography (Box 179, Folder 21)
      - Eight Little Piggies, figures (Box 179, Folder 22)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript, Front Matter and Prologue (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript, Chapters 1-3 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 4-7 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 8-12 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 13-16 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 17-20 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 21-24 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 25-28 (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript and pasteups, Chapters 29-31 and Bibliography (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Eight Little Piggies, typescript, Index (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Eight Little Piggies, galley proofs, captions (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Front Matter and Prologue (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 1-7 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 8-12 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 13-16 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 17-20 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 21-24 (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 25-28 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Chapters 29-31 and Bibliography (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), Index (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (first pass), captions (Box 181, Folder 8)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Front Matter and Prologue (Box 181, Folder 9)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 1-3 (Box 181, Folder 10)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 4-7 (Box 181, Folder 11)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 8-10 (Box 181, Folder 12)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 11-12 (Box 181, Folder 13)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 13-16 (Box 181, Folder 14)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 17-20 (Box 181, Folder 15)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 21-24 (Box 181, Folder 16)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 25-28 (Box 181, Folder 17)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (second pass), Chapters 29-31 and Bibliography (Box 181, Folder 18)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Title Page and Copyright (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Front Matter and Prologue (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 1-3 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 4-7 (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 8-12 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 13-16 (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 17-20 (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 21-24 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - Eight Little Piggies, master galley proof set (confirmation), Chapters 25-28 (Box 182, Folder 9)